<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.github.waveformplotter</id>
    <name>Waveform Plotter</name>
    <vendor>waveform-plotter</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[
        Real-time waveform plotter for embedded debugging in CLion.

        <b>Key Features:</b>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Passive Mode</b> — Automatically captures Watch variables on breakpoint/step pause events</li>
            <li><b>Live Watch</b> — Non-invasive real-time memory monitoring via OpenOCD Telnet (CPU keeps running)</li>
            <li><b>FFT Spectrum Analysis</b> — One-click time/frequency domain switching with Hanning window and dB magnitude spectrum</li>
            <li><b>ELF Symbol Resolution</b> — Zero-pause variable address resolution from ELF symbol table</li>
            <li><b>Multi-channel</b> — Up to 8 channels with pan, zoom, crosshair tooltip, and CSV export</li>
        </ul>

        Designed for OpenOCD / DAP-Link / ST-Link users.
        CLion's native Live Watches only supports J-Link/ST-Link — this plugin fills the gap for CMSIS-DAP debuggers.
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <b>v1.3.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Real-time X-axis</b> — True time-based X-axis replacing sample index, oscilloscope-style negative time (latest = 0)</li>
            <li><b>Auto-adaptive time units</b> — ms/μs toggle button, friendly 1-2-5 grid intervals like professional oscilloscopes</li>
            <li><b>Smart auto-tracking</b> — Auto-fit all data by default, sliding window after zoom, mouse-anchored zoom</li>
            <li><b>Larger buffer</b> — Data buffer increased to 10000 samples (200s at 50Hz)</li>
        </ul>

        <b>v1.3.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li><b>High-Speed Sampling (HSS)</b> — Byte-level bulk I/O replaces character-by-character reading, zero-allocation prompt scanning, sampling rate up to 2000 Hz</li>
            <li><b>Pre-compiled parsing</b> — OpenOCD response regex compiled once, reused across all samples</li>
            <li><b>Reusable read buffer</b> — Pre-allocated 4KB byte buffer eliminates GC pressure in sampling hot path</li>
        </ul>

        <b>v1.2.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li><b>FFT Spectrum Analysis</b> — Time/FFT one-click toggle, Cooley-Tukey radix-2 FFT with Hanning window, dB magnitude spectrum display</li>
            <li><b>Performance</b> — FFT result caching (recompute only on data change), Hanning window precomputation, work array reuse, BasicStroke caching</li>
            <li><b>DataBuffer versioning</b> — Atomic version counter for efficient cache invalidation</li>
        </ul>

        <b>v1.1.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Live Watch via OpenOCD Telnet with ELF symbol resolution</li>
            <li>Editor right-click "Add to Waveform Plotter" action</li>
            <li>Telnet pipelining + TCP_NODELAY for precision sampling</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.xdebugger</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.clion</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.nativeDebug</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="Waveform Plotter"
                    anchor="bottom"
                    factoryClass="com.github.waveformplotter.WaveformToolWindowFactory"
                    icon="/icons/waveform.svg"/>

        <projectService serviceImplementation="com.github.waveformplotter.WaveformConfigService"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <action id="WaveformPlotter.AddToPlotter"
                class="com.github.waveformplotter.AddToPlotterAction"
                text="Add to Waveform Plotter"
                description="Add selected variable to Waveform Plotter">
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>
